as the first foreign invested life
insurance Enterprise operating in
Vietnam since
1999 Manu life Vietnam is currently the
largest insurer in terms of total
investment
Capital with the mission of being a
trusted life partner the company is
investing heavily in technology to
deliver Innovative life insurance
services and solutions that enable the
people of Vietnam to live better every
day over the past few years man life
Vietnam has partnered with Hitachi
Digital Services Vietnam a trusted
digital Solutions provider to enhance
Business Development and provide
exceptional experiences for
customers at manual life uh one of our
core values is obsessing about customers
and uh we are focusing on building a
knowledgeable and uh dedicated team that
provides customers with simple efficient
and quick
Solutions and uh I strongly believe that
partnering with Hitachi Digital Services
Vietnam will help us transform our
journey uh to create value both for our
business and our
customers starting from 2019 uh Hitachi
Digital Services Vietnam has joined with
manual life in implementing numerous
technology projects Rel to customer
experience enhancement uh application
migration and and end to integration and
automation pertaining to operation
execution and big data analytics and
totaling about 30
projects there are highlight projects
between Mana life and Hitachi Digital
Services
Vietnam first integrating customer
systems with online payment companies
saves time and boosts customer
satisfaction second building system data
links to enhanc customer care improve
the efficiency of customer service staff
and boost business
Effectiveness third integrating and
transforming data between internal
systems ensures consistency and
integrity with partner Bank systems
supporting business requirements within
designated time frames fourth building
an endtoend training management system
ensures rapid evaluation of training
results enabling Swift and timely
enhancement of agent
proficiency DTI Digital Services Vietnam
is always eager to meet and exchange
ideas and solutions uh with manual
life's it team uh offering technical
support and proactively proposing um
Advanced Technical Solutions to meet the
specific needs of the insurance
industry
for at H Digital Services Vietnam we are
eager to accompany clients on their
digital transformation Journey bringing
valuable benefits to both Enterprises
and users helping right business growth
working with man life our team consists
of experience Engineers who are always
ready to listen and support in
digitizing processes standardizing
procedures enhancing team capabilities
and most importantly improving user
experiences with Advanced Technologies
[Music]